<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>6.9 on Home</title>
    <link>/updates/6.9/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 6.9 on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/updates/6.9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Career stats</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/career/</guid>
      <description>This page shows statistics of players&amp;rsquo; battles fought during their Blitz &amp;ldquo;career&amp;rdquo; until the end of update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of total battles per player in the end of the update 6.9. An average player has played 4887 battles by the end of update 6.9. Median battle count was 2430 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) was 163018 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier X statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/10/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier X during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 115 battles. Median was 45 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 5019 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier X Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/10/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier X during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.9</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.9. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned.
Battles per Player The graph shows the number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9. On average, players played 383 battles. Median was 236 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 30 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier IX statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/9/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier IX during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 104 battles. Median was 54 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 3986 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier IX Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/9/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier IX during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics by tier</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/</guid>
      <description>Update 6.9 This page shows various statistics per tier played.
Average tier WR vs average tier This graph shows player WR vs. average tier during the update 6.9. Minimum 50 battles required.
Share of players per WR per tier This chart shows share of players with certain WR (bar color-code) at certain tier (x-axis). Each players&amp;rsquo; battles at different tiers have been taken into account as long as the player as at least 100 battles at a tier during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VIII statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/8/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier VIII during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 125 battles. Median was 64 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 3633 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VIII Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/8/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier VIII during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics by Region</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/region/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/region/</guid>
      <description>Update 6.9 This page shows statistics per Blitz servers/regions (EU, NA, ASIA, Russia) during update 6.9. Statistics for the Chinese server are not available via WG API.
Number of players This graphs shows players by region in the dataset who have played at least one game. Please note, this does not mean all the players per server, but just those who have been recorded in the BlitzAnalysiz database.
WR Distribution This graph shows how the players overall WR during update 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VII statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/7/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier VII during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 82 battles. Median was 42 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 3592 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VII Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/7/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier VII during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VI statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/6/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier VI during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 68 battles. Median was 29 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 3350 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier VI Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/6/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier VI during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier V statistics</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tiers/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tiers/5/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought at tier V during update 6.9.
Battles per player Number of battles fought per player during the update 6.9.
On average, players played 47 battles. Median was 15 and the largest number of battles recorded by a single player (in the dataset) during the update 6.9 was 3715 battles. The following tables shows battle counts by N% most inactive players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tier V Tanks</title>
      <link>/update/6.9/tanks/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/update/6.9/tanks/5/</guid>
      <description>Highest Average WR This graph shows the tanks with the highest average WR at tier V during update 6.9. Player WR denotes the tank&amp;rsquo;s players&amp;rsquo; average WR across all the tanks during the update. Only tanks with more than 50 players are listed. This may filter out few upcoming tanks that are being tested.
Highest Average WR - Table Average WR denotes average WR in a tank accross all the players during the update.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>