<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Update on Home</title>
    <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Update on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.6*</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.6/</guid>
      <description>Preliminary stats
This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.6 so far. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.5</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.5/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.5. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 452M battles by 610k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.4</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.4/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.4. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 218M battles by 491k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.3</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.3/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.3. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 230M battles by 484k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.2</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.2/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.2. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 283M battles by 498k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.1</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.1/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.1. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 190M battles by 458k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 7.0</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/7.0/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 7.0. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 208M battles by 464k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.10</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.10/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.10. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 368M battles by 511k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.9</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.9/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.9. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 289M battles by 486k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.8</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.8/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.8. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 237M battles by 461k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.7</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.7/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.7. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 227M battles by 452k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.6</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.6/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.6. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 255M battles by 451k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.5</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.5/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.5. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 168M battles by 393k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.4</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.4/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.4. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 170M battles by 406k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.3</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.3/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.3. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 146M battles by 387k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.2</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.2/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.2. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 264M battles by 388k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.1</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.1/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.1. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 178M battles by 366k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.0</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.0/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.0. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 219M battles by 377k players recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
