<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Update on Home</title>
    <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Update on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.10</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.10/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.10. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 196650865 battles recorded by 402435 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.9</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.9/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.9. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 136633758 battles recorded by 355985 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.8</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.8/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.8. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 123642786 battles recorded by 338436 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.7</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.7/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.7. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 126377371 battles recorded by 329556 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.6</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.6/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.6. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 121576864 battles recorded by 304218 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.5</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.5/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.5. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 72904785 battles recorded by 260865 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.4</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.4/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.4. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 87183548 battles recorded by 266703 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.3</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.3/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.3. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 76071454 battles recorded by 251951 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.2</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.2/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.2. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 101541159 battles recorded by 225605 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.1</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.1/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.1. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 80569277 battles recorded by 217587 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 6.0</title>
      <link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/6.0/</guid>
      <description>This page list statistics of battles fought during 6.0. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not cumululative/total/lifetime stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 85237844 battles recorded by 205067 players.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>