<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Update on Home</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/</link><description>Recent content in Update on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blitzanalysiz.com/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Update 9.7</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.7/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.7. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 472M battles by 1.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.6</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.6/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.6. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 308M battles by 480k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.5</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.5/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.5. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 102M battles by 446k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.4</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.4/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.4. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 127M battles by 454k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.3</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.3/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.3. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 109M battles by 452k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.2</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.2/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.2. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 171M battles by 519k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.1</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.1/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.1. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 112M battles by 478k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 9.0</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/9.0/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 9.0. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 120M battles by 490k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.10</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.10/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.10/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.10. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 150M battles by 497k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.9</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.9/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.9. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 129M battles by 487k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.8</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.8/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.8. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 128M battles by 485k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.7</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.7/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.7. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 118M battles by 477k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.6</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.6/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.6. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 173M battles by 497k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.5</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.5/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.5. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 118M battles by 451k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.4</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.4/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.4. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 105M battles by 403k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.3</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.3/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.3. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 139M battles by 402k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.2</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.2/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.2. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 107M battles by 400k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.1</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.1/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.1. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 125M battles by 415k players recorded.</description></item><item><title>Update 8.0</title><link>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blitzanalysiz.com/update/8.0/</guid><description>Statistics of battles fought during update 8.0. All the stats (WR, damage, battles, etc.) refer to stats during the update, not career stats unless otherwise mentioned. In total, there were 152M battles by 477k players recorded.</description></item></channel></rss>